{
    "question": "Bahasan Inggris nya kamu sedang apa sekarang\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p>What are you doing now?</p>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>What Are You Doing? </p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Utu lah Arti nya jika translate kedalam bhsa Inggris Kawan</p><p>maaf jika salah</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "last-saturday-my-sister-dina-did-something-funny-she-got-up-ve-403",
            "question": "Last Saturday, my sister Dina, did    something funny. She got up very late, at\r\nsix. She ran fast to the bathroom. She took\r\nvery quick bath, got dressed, took her bag,\r\nand ran off to school. She did not even have\r\nbreakfast. After walking for five minutes,\r\nshe noticed that no other children were\r\ngoing to school. Soon she realized it was\r\nSaturday! So she walked back home. We\r\nlaughed at her when she got home. She also\r\nlaughed at herself.\r\n8. Whatkind of the text is it?\r\na. Recount text\r\nb. Descriptive text\r\nc. Narrative text\r\nd. Procedure text\r\n9. The purpose of the text is ...?\r\na. Entertain the readers\r\nb. Describe something\r\nc. Tell past event\r\nd. How to make something\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>8. A. recount text</p><p>9. C. tell past event</p><p></p><p>semoga terbantu, maap kalo salah. Kalo bener jangan lupa jadikan jawaban tercerdas yak\u270c</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>8.a recount text maaf kalo salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "9-choose-the-correct-sentence-below-she-is-tell-them-the-funny-895",
            "question": "9. Choose the correct sentence below!    She is tell them the funny story\r\nb. She telling them the funny story\r\nC. She is telling them the funny story\r\nd. She telling is them the funny story\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>C. she is telling then the funny story</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p> maaf kalau salah, semangat belajar nya</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "what-was-engelbarts-opinion-obout-mankids-problems-compered-to-966",
            "question": "What was engelbart,s opinion obout mankid,s problems compered to their abilities to solve them answer?    \u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Apa pendapat engelbart tentang masalah manusia dibandingkan dengan kemampuan mereka untuk menyelesaikannya?</p><p></p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>artinya</p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p>semoga membantu</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ana-arrange-the-words-to-be-good-sentence-me-delicious-gi-473",
            "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627    Arrange the words to be good sentence!\r\nMe - delicious - give - she-food - her\r\n4.\r\n5.\r\nBag is Rp 250.000\r\nWallet is Rp 150.000\r\nBag is..........\r\n..........than wallet ( expensive)\r\nWallet Is...........than bag (cheap)\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>\u2022 She give me her delicious food.</p><p>\u2022 Bag is <strong>more </strong><strong>expensive </strong>than wallet.</p><p>\u2022 Wallet is <strong>cheaper </strong>than bag</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p></p><p>Susunlah kata-kata tersebut menjadi kalimat yang baik!</p><p>Saya - enak - beri - dia-makanan - dia</p><p>4.</p><p>5.</p><p>Tas seharga Rp 250.000</p><p>Dompet Rp 150.000</p><p>Tas adalah..........</p><p>..........daripada dompet (mahal)</p><p>Dompet Is...........daripada tas (murah)</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "it-is-a-vehicle-it-is-big-and-199",
            "question": "It is a vehicle. it is big and?..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>its a car</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf kalau salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "do-you-think-its-important-to-educate-people-about-endanger-spec-462",
            "question": "Do you think it's important to educate people about endanger species?    a.\r\n\r\nNot, it isn't.\r\n\r\nb.\r\n\r\nNo important.\r\n\r\nc.\r\n\r\nYes, it is.\r\n\r\nd.\r\n\r\nYes, there are not.\r\n\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>The answer is C. Yes, it is</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>c.</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>yes,it is</p><p>ratinya ya itu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "dimas-do-you-have-favorite-novels-rino-thave-two-favorite-novels-722",
            "question": "Dimas Do you have favorite novels?    Rino Thave two favorite novels. The llounted House\r\nand The Secret Place\r\nDimas What kind of novel are they?\r\nRino The Hounted House is a horror novel, and\r\nThe Secret Place is a detective story\r\nDimas Which one is thicker?\r\nRino \u00b7 The Haunted House has 50 pages, but the\r\nSecret Place has 75 pages,\r\nDimas How much did you buy those novels?\r\nRino : The Haunted House is Rp. 35.000, and The\r\nSecret Place is Rp. 125.000\r\nDimas: I like detective story, too. May I borrow yours\r\nsometimes?\r\nRino Certainly! You may come to my house because\r\nI have more interesting story books to read\r\n26. Who likes detective story?\r\nA Dimas.\r\nC None\r\nB. Rino\r\nD. Dimas and Rino\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. Dimas </p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>karena di situ  Dimas bilang \"i like detective story&#039;\"</p><p>maaf kalau salah ya, semangat belajar nya </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "you-an-old-table-533",
            "question": "You....... an old table\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>You....... an old table\u200b</p><p>You <strong>have </strong>an old table.</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Jawaban pada kalimat di atas dicetak tebal dan merupakan bentuk Simple Present Tense karena menjelaskan fakta. Jika subjek nya adalah kata You, maka harus memakai kata kerja Have yang artinya memiliki.</p><p>Semoga membantu ya.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "russia-is-thecountry-in-the-world-655",
            "question": "Russia is the...country in the world",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>largest</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Rusia adalah negara terbesar di dunia</p><p></p><p></p><p>semoga membantu:)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "17-rey-what-is-your-favorite-menu-at-janji-jiwa-dinda-i-lik-325",
            "question": "17. Rey    : What is your favorite menu at Janji Jiwa?\r\nDinda : I like brown sugar milk tea with cincau.\r\nRey : How does it taste?\r\nDinda : .... It is my favorite drink.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p></p><p>it taste good,</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>kalo salah aku ga nanggung :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}